Guide to the Herman F. Mark Collection RG.002
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series X: Personal items and Miscellaneous, 9651
  - Subseries A: Desk drawer realia, 6478
    - Set of two key fobs with "Dr. H Mark", undated; 9662 (Box 27, Object 6)
    - Plastic cylinder, undated; 9884 (Box 27, Object 7)
    - Plastic in petri dish labeled "Hema", undated; 9885 (Box 27, Object 8)
    - Birthday candles and holders, undated; 9663 (Box 27, Object 9)
    - Calculator, undated; 9664 (Box 27, Object 10)
    - Metal pieces in envelope, undated; 9665 (Box 27, Object 11)
    - Cologne, undated; 9666 (Box 27, Object 12)
    - Polarizing film, undated; 9667 (Box 27, Object 13)
    - Three beakers, undated; 9668 (Box 27, Object 14)
    - Buttons in envelope, undated; 9669 (Box 27, Object 15)
    - Oxford copy holder, undated; 9886 (Box 27, Object 16)
    - Magnifying glass, undated; 9887 (Box 27, Object 17)
  - Subseries B: Personal, financial and medical records, 9652
    - Personal (contains bank statements, correspondence, memberships), circa 1991-1992; 9691 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Personal 1990, 9692 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Condolences, 1992; 9693 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Symposium, regrets, 1989; 9700 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Mark Estate, 1992; 9694 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Bank statements, 1992; 9724 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Payments, 1992, 9725 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Receipts, 1992, 9726 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Tax forms and bank statements, 1991-1992; 9723 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Rents, 1990, 9698 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Taxes, 1989-1991, 9699 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Work sheets, 1988, 9888 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Bank statements, 1988, 9889 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Payments, 1988, 9890 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Receipts, 1988, 9891 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Receipts, January-April 1988, 9892 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Receipts, May-August 1988, 9893 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Receipts, September-December 1988, 9894 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, 1987, 9895 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous receipts, 1981-1990; undated; 9712 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Medical, 1990-1992; 9701 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Medicare, 1989-1991; 9702 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous, 9653
    - Air clubs, 1978-1992; 9713 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Maps and train timetables, undated; 9714 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Magazines, 1998; 9727 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous documents and publications, undated; 9896 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous documents, undated; 9709 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated; 9710 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Numbered ink drawing, undated; 9711 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Herman Mark's suitcase (containing shirt, tie, and sweater), undated; 9715 (Box unboxed)
    - Herman Mark's leather tote bag, undated; 9716 (Box unboxed)
- Series XI: Collection provenance and information, 6480
  - Austrian National Library, 1992; 9720 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Herman Mark Collection (Heather Walters), 2001; 9721 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Herman Mark Collection (Lindsay Anderberg, Hans Mark, Jana Richman), 2013-2014; 9722 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Series XII: Objects that Need Conservation
  Accruals
  Tentative series of miscellaneous objects that belonged to Mark that require conservation.
  These miscellaneous items are housed in 7 boxes on bay 33 shelves 7B, 6A and 7A.
  - Resin/Enamel Rectangular Paperweight, undated (Box 40, Object 1)
  - Framed CIRFS Medal, undated (Box 40, Object 2)
  - Swiss Clock, undated (Box 40, Object 3)
  - Circular Mirror, undated (Box 41, Object 1)
  - Framed 'Republique Française' Medal, undated (Box 42, Object 1)
  - 90th Birthday Plaque, 1985-11 (Box 42, Object 2)
  - General Electric World Clock, undated (Box 43, Object 1)
  - Sigma Xi Award, 1970-06-02 (Box 44, Object 1)
  - Ceremonial Hat, undated (Box 45, Object 1)
  - New Years Lantern Slides, undated (Box 46, Object 1)